Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- A: A Dybbuk Show / B: Cagan Family Show: Three Generations of Social Activism with Jesse Cagan, Leslie Cagan and Joanna Cagan [1997-036], 1997 November 16; 1997 November 23; cuid33833 (Box 4, Audiocassette 718_0125)
  Duration: 1:58:39, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; High Amount of Hiss During Program; Dropout at Start of Side B During Program
- A: Lawrence Graver on Anne Frank; Workfare March; Metropolitan Klezmer with Eve Sicular and Debra Karpal / B: Israel Conversion Debate [1997-017], 1997 December 7; 1997 December 14; cuid33834 (Box 4, Audiocassette 718_0106)
  Duration: 1:59:32, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
- A: Shtell Books / B: Hanukkah Show: Arthur Waskow, Joan Nathan, and Great Small Works Performance [1996-016], 1997 December 21; 1997 December 28; cuid33835 (Box 3, Audiocassette 718_0105)
  Duration: 1:59:31, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; High Amount of Hum During Program
- In Gerangl: Gay/Lesbian Jewish Politics, circa 1998; cuid33836 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0373)
  Duration: 1:44:22, Preservation Note: Phasing During Program; High Amount of Buzz During Program; Static During Program
- In Gerangl: Liberation Theologies, circa 1998; cuid33837 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0374)
  Duration: 1:32:44, Preservation Note: Static During Program
- In Gerangl: Culture Wars, circa 1998; cuid33838 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0375)
  Duration: 1:41:01, Preservation Note: High Amount of Hum During Program; Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program; Channel Imbalance
- In Gerangl: Next Generation, circa 1998; cuid33839 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0376)
  Duration: 1:24:10, Preservation Note: Speed Fluctuations During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- In Gerangl: Racism - Current State of Struggle, circa 1998; cuid33840 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0377)
  Duration: 1:26:39, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; High Background Noise During Program; High Amount of Hum During Program
- In Gerangl: Continuation of Afternoon Plenary - Race Relations, Police Brutality I, circa 1998; cuid33841 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0378)
  Duration: 1:44:10, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- In Gerangl: Student Movements, circa 1998; cuid33842 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0379)
  Duration: 1:40:10, Preservation Note: Phasing During Program; High Amount of Buzz During Program; Static During Program; Left Channel Only From 00:23:06 Until End of Program on Side B During Program
- In Gerangl: Fighting Poverty, circa 1998; cuid33843 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0380)
  Duration: 1:25:10, Preservation Note: No Right Channel From 00:47:31 Until End of Program on Side A During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; Warble During Program
- In Gerangl: Fighting the Right, Afternoon Plenary - Beginning, circa 1998; cuid33844 (Box 11, Audiocassette 718_0381)
  Duration: 1:39:02, Preservation Note: Static During Program; High Amount of Hiss During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Reading [1998-002], 1998-01; cuid33845 (Box 21, Reel 718_0933)
  Duration: 0:26:57, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- A: Jewish Film Festival: Hollywood Blacklist / B: Smithsonian, New Israel Fund [1998-032], 1998 January 11; 1998 February 1; cuid33846 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0172)
  Duration: 1:59:48, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times; High Amount of Hiss During Program
- Remembering the Message of Abraham Joshua Heschel: Professor Susannah Heschel [1998-006], 1998-01-16; cuid33847 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0146)
  Duration: 1:35:12, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance; High Amount of Hiss During Program; Phasing During Program; Static During Program
- Remembering the Message of Abraham Joshua Heschel: Rev. William Sloane Coffin, Jr and U.S. Senator Paul Wellstone [1998-007], 1998-01-16 (Box 5, Item 718_0147)
- A: Martin Luther King Jr., Abraham Joshua Heschel / B: Abraham Lincoln Brigade [1998-071-z], 1998 February 8; 1998 March 29; cuid33848 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0208)
  Duration: 2:04:40, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Clicks and Pops During Program
- In Gerangl: Activist Legacies of the Bund, Tape 3 [1998-025], 1998 March 1; cuid33849 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0165)
  Duration: 0:42:38, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- A: In Gerangl: Activist Legacies of the Bund, Tape 1 - Zemanowicz/Soyer / B: Soyer [1998-033], 1998-03-01; cuid33850 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0173)
  Duration: 1:00:38, Preservation Note: Dropouts at End of Side A During Program; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- In Gerangl: Activist Legacies of the Bund Tape, 2 [1998-034], 1998-03-01; cuid33851 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0174)
  Duration: 0:58:53, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Buzz on Side B at 1:03
- In Gerangl: Activist Legacies of the Bund, Tape 4 - Youth Theatre Performance/Buhle [1998-035], 1998-03-01; cuid33852 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0175)
  Duration: 0:33:47, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- In Gerangl: Activist Legacies of the Bund, Tape 5 - Final Panel [1998-036], 1998-03-01; cuid33853 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0176)
  Duration: 1:28:24, Preservation Note: Phasing During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- A: Joseph Skibbel and Yaron Ezrahi / B: Crisis at CUNY [1998-070-z], 1998 March 1; 1998 March 15; cuid33854 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0207)
  Duration: 1:57:02, Preservation Note: Tape Re-Shelled; Broken Splices Repaired; Program Distorted at Times
- Emma Goldman 2 Hour Special [1998-069-z], 1998-03-08; cuid33855 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0206)
  Duration: 1:56:03, Preservation Note: Tape Re-Shelled; Broken Splices Repaired; Dropouts During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program; Static During Program
- Crisis at CUNY [1998-008], 1998-03-15; cuid33856 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0148)
  Duration: 0:56:17, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times; Phasing During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0158, 718_0159, 718_0160
- A: Crisis at CUNY / B: School Voucher Controversy [1998-018], 1998 March 15; 1998 April 11; cuid33857 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0158)
  Duration: 1:50:20, Preservation Note: Channel Imbalance; Program is Muffled; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0159, 718_0160, 718_0148, 718_0244, 718_0448
- A: School Voucher Controversy / B: Crisis at CUNY [1998-019], 1998 March 15; 1998 April 11; cuid33858 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0159)
  Duration: 1:50:42, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Simultaneous Programs on Side A
  Duplicate of 718_0158, 718_0160, 718_0148, 718_0244, 718_0448
- A: Crisis at CUNY / B: School Voucher Controversy [1998-020], 1998 March 15; 1998 April 11; cuid33859 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0160)
  Duration: 1:52:13, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Audible Print-Through During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0158, 718_0159, 718_0148, 718_0244, 718_0448
- The Foner Family Special: Jack Foner, Moe Foner, Henry Foner, and Eric Foner [1998-017], 1998-03-22; cuid33860 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0157)
  Duration: 2:02:53, Preservation Note: Phasing During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Clicks and Pops During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0171, 718_0161, 718_0203
- 2 Hour Foner Special (Damaged) [1998-021], 1998-03-22; cuid33861 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0161)
  Duration: 1:20:02, Preservation Note: Static During Program; High Amount of Hiss During Program; Speed Fluctuations During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0157, 718_0171, 718_0203
- The Foner Family Special: Jack Foner, Moe Foner, Henry Foner, and Eric Foner [1998-031], 1998-03-22; cuid33862 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0171)
  Duration: 1:56:48, Preservation Note: Channel Imbalance; Program Distorted at Times; High Amount of Hiss During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0157, 718_0161, 718_0203
- A: Foner Family Special [1998-068-z], 1998-03-22; cuid33863 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0203)
  Duration: 1:56:17, Preservation Note: Tape Re-Shelled; Broken Splices Repaired; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0157, 718_0161, 718_0171
- Hidden Jews: Christopher Hitchens on Madeleine Albright Story; Roderick Young at Congregation Beth Simchat Torah; Mark Robinson; Otto Maduro [1997-005], 1998-03-23; cuid33864 (Box 3, Audiocassette 718_0093)
  Duration: 1:03:00, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
- Co-host Henry Foner with Abraham Lincoln Brigade Veterans Moe Fishman, Abe Smorodin, and Harry Fisher [1998-113-z], 1998-03-29; cuid33865 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0410)
  Duration: 1:00:05, Preservation Note: Static During Program
- Rebecca Alpert; Laura Schere; Racial Justice Day Report [1998-014], 1998-04-05; cuid33866 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0154)
  Duration: 0:30:13, Preservation Notes: Side B is Blank; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Related to 718_0162, 718_0216, 718_0384, 718_0398
- Racial Justice Day Report; Barry Sisters Song, "Khad Gadyo" [1998-022], 1998 April 5; 1998 April 12; cuid33867 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0162)
  Duration: 1:59:57, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Clicks and Pops During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0216, 718_0384, 718_0398; Related to 718_0154
- A: Racial Justice Day, Rebecca Alpert, Laura Schere / B: Passover Music with Lorin Sklamberg [1998-079-z], 1998 April 5; 1998 April 12; cuid33868 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0216)
  Duration: 2:03:38, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Clicks and Pops During Program; Channel Imbalance; Warble During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0162, 718_0384, 718_0398; Related to 718_0154
- Zalmen Mlotek and Eleanor Reissa on Folksbiene's New Production, Sweet Dreams; Lorin Sklamberg with Hanukkah Music [1998-100-z], 1998-04-05; cuid33869 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0398)
  Duration: 0:57:45, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Title does not reflect content; Duplicate of 718_0162, 718_0216; Related to 718_0154, 718_0384
- Passover Music Show with Co-host Lorin Sklamberg [1998-087-z], 1998-04-12; cuid33870 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0384)
  Duration: 1:01:37, Preservation Note: Clicks and Pops During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Program Recorded at a Very High Level
  Duplicate of 718_0162, 718_0216, 718_0398
- Israel at 50 with Zeev Sternhall, Nathan Krystel; Holocaust Semantics [1998-023], 1998 April 19; 1998 April 26; cuid33871 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0163)
  Duration: 1:59:18, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0213, 718_0422, 718_0394
- A: Israel at 50 / B: Holocaust Semantics [1998-076-z], 1998 April 19; 1998 April 26; cuid33872 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0213)
  Duration: 1:59:37, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Warble During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0163, 718_0422, 718_0394
- Israel at 50 with Zeev Sternhell, Nathan Krystal, and Tom Abowd [1998-086-z], 1998-04-19; cuid33873 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0422)
  Duration: 0:59:17, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0163, 718_0213, 718_0394
- Ilan Stavans and Moacyr Scliar in Conversation [1998-084-z], 1998-04-21; cuid33874 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0420)
  Duration: 1:17:24, Preservation Note: Channel Imbalance; Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program; Digital Dropouts and Skipping at 00:18:02
- Holocaust Semantics: Tom Freudenheim, Sam Anderson, Karen Ishizuka, Nitzan Aviram, Igal Izraty [1998-097-z], 1998-04-26; cuid33875 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0394)
  Duration: 0:59:35, Preservation Note: Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0163, 718_0213, 718_422
- Tom Segev [1998-011], 1998-05-04; cuid33876 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0151)
  Duration: 1:29:04, Preservation Note: Phasing During Program; Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- Congregation B'nai Jeshurun - Tom Segev, Part 2 [1998-003], 1998-05-06; cuid33877 (Box 21, Reel 718_0934)
  Duration: 0:28:35, Preservation Note: Static During Program; High Amount of Hum During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Dropouts During Program
- Congregation B'nai Jeshurun - Rashid Khalidi, Part 1 [1998-004], 1998-05-06; cuid33878 (Box 21, Reel 718_0935)
  Duration: 0:22:22, Preservation Note: High Amount of Hum During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
- Congregation B'nai Jeshurun, Selections from Response to Segev on Support for Nazis and Holocaust - Rashid Khalidi, Part 3 [1998-005], 1998-05-06; cuid33879 (Box 21, Reel 718_0936)
  Duration: 0:03:38, Preservation Note: High Amount of Hum During Program; Static During Program
- Marathon Show: Hollywood Blacklist and McCarthyism [1998-015], 1998-05-10; cuid33880 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0155)
  Duration: 2:03:50, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0214, 718_0412, 718_0413
- Marathon Show: The Hollywood Blacklist and McCarthyism [1998-077-z], 1998-05-10; cuid33881 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0214)
  Duration: 2:03:28, Preservation Note: Speed Fluctuations at Start of Side A During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0155, 718_0412, 718_0413
- Marathon Show: Hollywood Blacklist and McCarthyism, Part 1 [1998-115-z], 1998-05-10; cuid33882 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0412)
  Duration: 1:01:34, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0155, 718_0214; Related to 718_0413
- Marathon Show: Hollywood Blacklist and McCarthyism, Part 2 [1998-117-z], 1998-05-10; cuid33883 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0413)
  Duration: 0:59:44, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0155, 718_0214; Related to 718_0412
- Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev at B'nai Jeshurun Forum Alternating Narratives: Palestinian and Israeli Views of 1948 [1998-095-z], 1998-05-24; cuid2613 (Box 5, Item 718_0164, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_611)
  Said, Shohat, Finkelstein; Khalidi, Segev — Edward Said, Ella Shohat, Norman Finkelstein - speaking at Columbia forum on the consequences of 1948 // A: Edward Said, Ella Shohat, Norman Finkelstein at Columbia Forum on Consequences of 1948 / B: Rashid Khalidi, Tom Segev [1998-024]
- Edward Said, Ella Shohat, Norman Finkelstein at Columbia Forum on Consequences of 1948 [1998-096-z], 1998-05-17; cuid33884 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0393)
  Duration: 1:01:22, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev at B'nai Jeshurun Forum Alternating Narratives: Palestinian and Israeli Views of 1948 [1998-095-z], 1998-05-24; cuid33885 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0392)
  Duration: 0:57:18, Preservation Note: Program Recorded at a Very Low Level; High Background Noise During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Digital Errors During Program
- Latino-Hasidic Housing Conflict in Williamsburg; Alisa Lebow and Cynthia Madansky on Treyf; Secular Humanist Judaism [1998-028], 1998 May 31; 1998 August 23; cuid33886 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0168)
  Duration: 1:54:22, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Echo on Side B
  Duplicate of 718_0167, 718_0215, 718_0391
- A: Latino-Hasidic Housing Conflict in Williamsburg; Alisa Lebow and Cynthia Madansky on Treyf / B: Secular Humanist Judaism [1998-078-z], 1998 May 31; 1998 August 23; cuid33887 (Box 7, Audiocassette 718_0215)
  Duration: 1:54:47, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0167, 718_0168, 718_0391
- Latino-Hasidic Housing Conflict in Williamsburg; Alisa Lebow and Cynthia Madansky on Treyf [1998-094-z], 1998-05-31; cuid33888 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0391)
  Duration: 0:59:26, Preservation Note: Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0167, 718_0168, 718_0215
- Judith Sloan with Scott Blakeman and Julie Goldman [1998-026], 1998 June 7; cuid33889 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0166)
  Duration: 1:03:18, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0212
- A: Judith Sloan / B: Ivri-Nasawi and "Sephardic Voices" Tribute, 1998 June 7; 1998 June 14; cuid33890 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0169)
  Duration: 1:55:48, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Interference During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0211, 718_0390
- Judith Sloan [1998-075-z], 1998-06-07; cuid33891 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0212)
  Duration: 1:04:01, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0166
- Ivri-Nasawi and "Sephardic Voices" Tribute [1998-074-z], 1998-06-14; cuid33892 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0211)
  Duration: 1:00:59, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank
  Duplicate of 718_0169, 718_0390
- Ivri-Nasawi and "Sephardic Voices" Tribute [1998-093-z], 1998-06-14; cuid33893 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0390)
  Duration: 1:01:05, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Program Recorded at a Very High Level; Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0169, 718_0211
- Ashkenaz Jewish Poetry; Gay Pride Show [1998-050], 1998 June 21; 1998 July 5; cuid33894 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0190)
  Duration: 1:46:16, Preservation Note: Echo During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Warble During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0210, 718_0417, 718_0423
- A: Ashkenaz Jewish Poetry / B: Gay Pride Show [1998-073-z], 1998 June 21; 1998 July 5; cuid33895 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0210)
  Duration: 2:00:18, Preservation Note: Echo During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Warble During Program at Start of Side B
  Duplicate of 718_0190, 718_0417, 718_0423
- Askenaz Jewish Poetry [1998-080-z], 1998-06-21; cuid33896 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0417)
  Duration: 0:56:46
  Duplicate of 718_0190, 718_0210
- Gay Pride Show with Dr. Tal Jarus-Hakak and Saul Mizrachi, 1998-07-05; cuid33897 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0423)
  Duration: 1:01:06, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Program Recorded at a Very High Level
  Duplicate of 718_0190, 718_210
- A: Disability Rights and Cemetery Workers Strike / B: Jews and Anarchism [1998-046], 1998-07-12; 1998-07-19; cuid2615 (Box 6, Item 718_0186, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_613)
  Disability Rights and Cemetary Workers' Lockout with Freda Zames, Disabled in Action, and Avi Lyon of the Jewish Labor Committee, and Jack Ryan, President, Local 74, SEIU. Jews and Anarchism Co-Host Laura Schere
- Disability Rights; Jews and Anarchism [1998-048], 1998-07-12; 1998-07-19; cuid2614 (Box 6, Item 718_0188, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_612)
  Jews and Anarchism Co-Host Laura Schere, Disability Rights and Cemetary Workers' Lockout with Freda Zames, Disabled in Action, and Avi Lyon of the Jewish Labor Committee, and Jack Ryan, President, Local 74, SEIU
- A: Disability Rights and Cemetery Workers Strike / B: Jews and Anarchism [1998-072-z], 1998 July 12; 1998 July 19; cuid33898 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0209)
  Duration: 2:00:18, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Program Recorded at a Very High Level
  Duplicate of 718_0418, 718_0400
- Disability Rights and Jewish Cemetery Strike with Frieda Zames, Avi Lyon, and Jack Ryan, 1998-07-12; cuid33899 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0418)
  Duration: 0:59:13
  Duplicate of 718_0209
- Jews and Anarchism: Laura Schere and Aaron Taub with Paul Buhle, Clara Solomon, Sidney Solomon, and Nina Dibner [1998-103-z], 1998-07-19; cuid33900 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0400)
  Duration: 0:59:41, Preservation Note: Dropouts During Program; Static During Program
- Music Marathon: Conclusion '63, 73, Music [1998-016], 1998-07-26; cuid33901 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0156)
  Duration: 1:01:24, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Clicks and Pops During Program
- Music Show: Lorin Sklamberg, The Escape Artist; Rabbi Haim Dov Beliak and Rabbi Jeffrey Goldstein [1998-047], 1998 July 26; 1998 August 2; cuid33902 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0187)
  Duration: 1:47:29, Preservation Note: Clicks and Pops During Program; Program Distorted at Times; Channel Imbalance
  Duplicate of 718_0405, 718_0196, 718_0395
- A: Lorin Sklamberg / B: Moskowitz's Bingo/Judith Katz [1998-061], 1998 July 26; 1998 August 2; cuid33903 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0196)
  Duration: 1:50:02, Preservation Note: Clicks and Pops During Program; Program Distorted at Times; High Amount of Hiss During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0405, 718_0187, 718_0395
- Music Show: Lorin Sklamberg [1998-108-z], 1998-07-26; cuid33904 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0405)
  Duration: 0:48:12, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0187, 718_0196
- Irving Moskowitz Bingo Profits and West Bank Land; Interviews with Rabbi Haim Dov Beliak and Rabbi Jeffrey Goldstein [1998-098-z], 1998-08-02; cuid33905 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0395)
  Duration: 0:57:28, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0196, 718_0187
- Jews in Hungary; Jews and Hip Hop Show [1998-013], 1998 August 9; 1998 August 16; cuid33906 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0153)
  Duration: 2:00:14, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program; Channel Imbalance; Left channel echo on side A
  Duplicate of 718_0197, 718_0404, 718_0177, 718_0180, 718_0478
- A: Jews in Hungary / B: Jews in Hip Hop [1998-062], 1998 August 9; 1998 August 16; cuid33907 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0197)
  Duration: 2:03:37, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0153, 718_0404, 718_0177, 718_0180, 718_0478
- Jews in Hungary: Pearl Gluck, Gábor Szántó, Thomas Biro, and Agnes Peresztegi [1998-107-z], 1998-08-09; cuid33908 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0404)
  Duration: 0:59:54, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0153, 718_0197, 718_0478
- Jewish Hip Hop Show [1998-037], 1998-08-16; cuid33909 (Box 5, Audiocassette 718_0177)
  Duration: 1:02:04, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0153, 718_0197, 718_0180
- Jewish Hip Hop Show [1998-040], 1998 August 16; cuid33910 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0180)
  Duration: 1:02:11, Preservation Note: Static During Program; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0153, 718_0197, 718_0177
- Jews and Hip Hop: Co-host Jonathan Cohen with George Salmers and Nadav Samin [1998-099-z], 1998-08-16; cuid33911 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0396)
  Tape is Blank; No Digital Files Created
- Secular Humanism: Aaron Taub and Joe Dimo with Myrna Baron, Rhea Seagull, and Roberta Feinstein [1998-105-z], 1998-08-23; cuid33912 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0402)
  Duration: 0:58:53
- Non-Jews Play Jewish with Host Lorin Sklamberg [1998-060], 1998-08-30; cuid33913 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0195)
  Duration: 0:58:22, Preservation Note: Side B is Blank; Program Distorted at Times
  Duplicate of 718_0419, 718_0109
- Lorin Sklamberg Music [1998-082-z], 1998-08-30; cuid33914 (Box 12, Audiocassette 718_0419)
  Duration: 0:58:12, Preservation Note: Digital Errors During Program; Static During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0195, 718_0109
- Oslo: 5 Years, Immigrant Labor; Brooklyn's 9th Congressional District Primary, Jo-Ann Mort [1998-041], 1998 September 6; 1998 September 13; cuid33915 (Box 6, Audiocassette 718_0181)
  Duration: 1:45:31, Preservation Note: Program Distorted at Times; High Background Noise During Program; Echo During Program
  Duplicate of 718_0194, 718_0399, 718_040